motionmods.com 2011-10-20

# - MotionMods.com

**Information We Collect**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, or subscribe to any of our newsletters or mailing lists. You may, of course, visit and browse portions of our site anonymously.

**What We Use Your Information For**

The information we collect from you may be used to process transactions, delivering purchased product(s) or service(s), to send you information and updates pertaining to your order(s) or site usage, and occasionally to inform you of promotions, products and other things we believe to be relevant to you and your interests. 

**Cookies**

We use cookies (if enabled in your browser) that allow us to recognize your browser and remember information, for example, what items are in your shopping cart.

**Information Disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. We may release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.

**Third Party Links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging in and going to the 'Account Info' page.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act)- we do not knowingly or intentionally collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are intended for people who are at least 13 years of age or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions at <http://motionmods.com/terms>

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

This page contains the latest version of our privacy policy. If changes occur, they will be available here. 

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

http://motionmods.com  
455 Lakefield Rd  
Selmer, TN 38375  
USA  
sales (at) motionmods (dot) com
